Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, pre-1991; Series 1
  - Goodman, Corey, Metamorphosis and lack of nerve innervation in aneural limbs of the Urodele, Taricha Torosa.., 1972 [?] (Box 4)
  - Goodman, Laurie E., Identification and Isolation of the DNA polymerase III (po1C) Promoter in Bacillus subtilis.., June 1985 (Box 4)
  - Gordon, Joseph Robert, Production and deposition of glycosaminoglycan in the postnatal mammary gland.., May 1977 (Box 4)
  - Gordon, Lynn Kathryn, Appearance of surface immunoglobulin n B lymphocytes.., 1975 (Box 4)
  - Gottlieb, Sami Lynne, Maternal and Social Factors Affecting Stress Responsiveness in Infant Rats.., 1988 (Box 4)
  - Graham, Karen, Human Xanthine Oxidase: isolation and Partial Characterization from Milkwith Subsequent Raising of Polyclonal Antibodies.., 1988 (Box 4)
  - Grainger, Robert, Studies of Bleaching in Euglena gracilis: Light Intensity Dependence of Bleaching and Isolation of Resistant Mutant.., Spring 1970 (Box 4)
  - Greaves, Adrienne A., Growth Cone Retraction and a Rise in Calcium in response to Alph-BCP in Bag Cell Neurons of Aplysia californica.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Green, Daniel E. and Edward E. Luck, A comprehensive study of two distinct forms of the Decticine Katydid, Nebuda diabolica.., May 16, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Green, Douglas S., The evolutionary genetics of finite sized populations: Acomputer simulation.., March 31, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Greene, Warner C., Protein synthesis in nrmal and diabetic rat kidney ribosomes.., Spring 1971 (Box 4)
  - Griffin, Glyn Carol, Sucrose Malabsorption in the Pasted Adult Rat as reflected by H2 Excretion Analysis.., 1983 (Box 4)
  - Griffiths, David Wesley, The effects of 1,25-dihydroxycholecalciferol on the collagen synthesis of osteoblast-like cells of neonatal mice.., 1981 (Box 4)
  - Grymes, Rosalind A., see Suen, Patrick W.. (Box 4)
  - Hahn, George M., see Rahman, Maie A.. (Box 4)
  - Hamori, Charles J. (with Hendrik J. Vreman, Pamela A. Rodgers and David K. Stevenson), Zinc Protoporphyrin Inhibits CO Production in Rats.., 1988 (Box 4)
  - Hampp, Lydia T., Altered Structure of Two Intestinal brush Border Hydrolases in Human Diabetes Mellitus.., 1987 (Box 4)
  - Hanson, Barbara, Host Effects on the Integrity of DNA from UV-sensitive T4 Phage.., Spring 1970 (Box 4)
  - Haqq, Christopher M., Correlation of Cellular Repair of Pyrimidine Dimers with Tissue-Specific Gene Expression.., 1987 (Box 4)
  - Harney, Kimberly Susan, Development of a corticosterone implant for use in behavioral studies.., March 1977 (Box 4)
  - Harris, john M., The Health Effects of Air Pollution.., Spring 1970 (Box 4)
  - Harris, Ronald Morgan, A Nontransducable Suppressor Mutation in E. coli.., Spring 1970 (Box 4)
  - Harrison, David A., Involvement of Calcium, Magnesium and Manganese in Auxin and Fusicoccin Action.., June 1985 (Box 4)
  - Harvie, Christopher J., An Assay of the Utilization of 14-C Glycerol on the Basis of Oxygen Consumption in Anthopleura elegantissima.., March 1976 (Box 4)
  - Hauger, Steven H., Spectral Efficiency of Phototaxis ina Photonegative Moth: Perception of Infrared Radiation.., Winter 1974 (Box 4)
  - Hayashi, Robert J., Regulation of S-Adenosylmethionine in the Rat Adrenal Medulla.., May 1982 (Box 5)
  - Hayes, Jane Leslie, Orientation behavior of C. Eurytheme larvae: The midrib resting position of early instars.., 1975 (Box 5)
  - Hedges, Bruce E., The Structure of the Nicotinic Acetylcholine Receptor of Amphibia as Revealed by Cross-reacting Monoclonal Antibodies.., May 1982 (Box 5)
  - Heer, Eric Martin, Neuronal Cell-Surface Receptors in the Developing Mouse Cerebellum: structural Analysis of Ll Antigen.., February 1986 (Box 5)
  - Helfand, Stephen L., The dissociation and growth of ciliary ganglio cells in vitro.., 1975 (Box 5)
  - Helman, Terri Ann, Ontogenic appearance of sucrase in the jejunum of the rat: hormonal effects and intracellular distribution.., 1975 [?] (Box 5)
  - Henrikson, Kare Ann, Characterization of Mutations of the polC Gene in Bacillus subtilis.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Hepworth, Randall, Lysozyme secretion by mouse peritoneal macrophages infected by lactic dehydrogenase virus.., 1976 (Box 5)
  - Hetzler, Peter, The uptake of host-released ammonia by the endosymbiotic zooxanthellae of the sea anemone, Anthopleura elegantissima (Brandt, 1835).., June 1976 (Box 5)
  - Hinds, Heather L., Wilson's Disease: Studies of a Closely Lnked Polymorphic Marker: pCR1324., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Hintz, Susan Ruth, Recovery of Exogenous Heme as Carbon Monoxide and Biliary Heme in Adult Rats After Tin-Protoporphyrin Treatment.., 1987 (Box 5)
  - Hoch, Peter C., Pollination ecology in alpine Colorado with special reference to nectar.., April 27, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Hofstadter, Laura, Effects of EDTA on Escherichia Coli.., March 1972 (Box 5)
  - Hoft, Richard, Investigations into several aspects of Mammalian cell resistance to methotrexate.., May 1, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Holbrook, Karen A, Guanine Nucleotide Modulation of Serotonin Receptor Interactions.., 1984 (Box 5)
  - Holmes, Eli, Foraging Behaviors Among Different Age and Sex Classes of Rocky Mountain Goats.., 1988 (Box 5)
  - Holmkvist, Kristina A, Drought Tolerance of the Newly Described Resurrection Fern Pityrogramma triangularis.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Holsti, Matthew A., A developmentally Regulated Glycoprotein Expressed by Chicken Skeletal Muscle.., June 9, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Holt, Catherine, Investigation of the nature and location of the ultravioletblue light photoreceptor pigment system in neurospora crassa.., 1975 (Box 5)
  - Hong, Robert Allan, The effects of 5-flurouracil and 43 C(celsius) heat.., May 1977 (Box 5)
  - Hoover, Craig Alan, The Effects of Selective and Non-Selective Beta Blockade on Plasma Catecholamine Levels During Exercise.. (Box 5)
  - Howard, Daniel Joseph, The thermal biology of three montane species of butterflies.., May 1977 (Box 5)
  - Hoyden, Kenneth F., Fronal and infero-temporal cortices influences on cortex visual units. (Box 5)
  - Hsu, Frank J., Immunochemical Studies Utilizing Well-Defined Model Systems. 112P., graphs, illus., tables.., June 1982 (Box 5)
  - Hsu, Ricky K., The Correlation of DNA Repair Rates with Transcriptional Modulation of the Plasminogen Gene Family.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Hu, Eddie Hong Lung, Study of organ morphogenesis. (alsp preliminary draft)., Spring 1976 (Box 5)
  - Huang, Linda T., Possibility of Ionophore-Induced Heat-Shock Response in HA-1 Cells.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Hufty, Mary, Hereditary pancreatitis: a study of the genetics of four new kindreds.., April 24, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Hughes, Luman Harold, Circadian core body temperature rhythms in time-isolated humans with narcolepsy. 5p.., May 1979 (Box 5)
  - Hult, James E., Nitrogeneous Waste Products and Excretory Enzymes in the Marine Polychaete Cirriformia Spirabrancha.., May 1969 (Box 5)
  - Hunter, A.Decker, Accumlation and effects of DDT in cotton (Gossypium herbaceum) leaves.., Spring 1970 (Box 5)
  - Hurvits, Susan Avital, Role of the denV gene product of T4 phage in repair of furocoumarin adducts in DNA. vi, 35 leaves: ill. Graphs. Tables. Bibliography: P.34-35., 1981 (Box 5)
  - Hwang, Loris Yehshiun, Effects of Various Foraginf Demands on Adrenocotical Activity and Behavior of Mother-Infant Squirrel Monkey Dyads.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Hyman, Jon L., Immunotherapy of Brain Tumor Using Corybacterium Parvum and Repeated Doses of IL-2 in Mince.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Imsand, Patricia, Fluorescence in Balanophyllia Elegans; an account of an investigation.., June 1970 (Box 5)
  - Ingram, David, Temperature relations and freezing hardness in Sequioa Sempervirens and Pseudotsuga Menziesii., 1978 (Box 5)
  - Jackson, Debra Francine, The elucidation of the banding pattern of the long arm of the human X chromosome.., 1973 (Box 5)
  - Jacobs, Elizabeth A., Conditioned Taste Aversion and Pituitary-Adrenal Activity in Preweanling Rats: The Ontogenetic Trend in Conditioned Corticosterone Response Over 12,14,16,18, and 20 Days of Age.., 1987 (Box 5)
  - Jacobs, Marc David, Adaptation and Constrint in Photoperiodic Alternation of Thermoregulatory Phenotypes.., 1988 (Box 5)
  - Jessen, Tom, Body -- Brain -- Culture.., Spring 1970 (Box 5)
  - Jiminez, Marcus A., Cell Cycle Effects on Transient and Stable Expressions of Plasmid DNA in Human Cells.., June 9, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Jolly, Jenora, Immunocytochemical Study of Phosphorylated and Dephosphorylated intermediate Filament Proteins of the CNS.., June 1986 (Box 5)
  - Jones, Kendall Maurice, A comparison of fluorescent antibody and radioimmunoassay techniques in urinary tract infections.., 1981 (Box 5)
  - Jones, Kristina Niovi, Mating Behavior of Euphydryas Editha: Determinants of Male and Female Reproductive Fitness.., 1984 (Box 5)
  - Jones, Mark C., Two in vitro systems for studying the initial interaction of smooth and rough strains of salmonell typhimurium with mouse macrophage-like cells.., May 24, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Jurisson, Mary L., The LD50/160 for one, two, and three month old lung-irradiated mice.., 1976 (Box 5)
  - Kam, Jeffrey Carter, PALA and thymidine as possible chemotherapeutic agents in the treatment of cancer.., 1980 (Box 6)
  - Kamel, Luca Christopher, Studies on the Development Arrest in Drosophila Pseudoobscura Pupae. (Box 5)
  - Kaufman, Dan S., Use of Anti-L3T4 and Anti-Ia Treatments for Prolongation of Xenogeneic Islet Transplants.., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Kedes, Dean Hamilton, The role of nerve growth factor plasma membrane receptor occupancy in the stimulation of alpha-aminoisobutyric acid uptake in PC12 cells.., 1981 (Box 6)
  - Keeley, Robert Denius, Purification of Glial Fibrillary Acidic Protein from Human Brain White Matter with multiple Sclerosis and Characterization of Calcium-Mediated Degradation Products.., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Keiler, Kenneth C., Regulationof Gene Expression of DNA Polymerase a and Primase Through Cellular Differentiation.., June 1989 (Box 13)
  - Keith, Bradley J., The relationship between cyclic AMP levels, growth rate, and cell density in Escherichia coli growing in continuous culture.., October 1979 (Box 6)
  - Kelley, Scott Donald, The effect of x-irradiation on cell loss from experimental mous tumors, as determined by the 125IUdR method.., 1980 (Box 6)
  - Kempen, John Harold, The Effects of Harvester Ant and Pocket Gopher Distubance on Soil Characteristics in a Central California Serpentine Grassland.., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Kephart, Donald Gary, Competitive relationships among several species of snakes on and around Jasper Ridge.., May 1977 (Box 6)
  - Kern, Margaret, Kinetics of the Conversion of Analogs of Indole to the Corresponding Tryptophan Derivitives.., September 1973 (Box 6)
  - Khanna, Hanwal, A (subcript a): A (subscript b) complexes composed of molecules of different haplotypes.., 1980 (Box 6)
  - Kim, Charles Bryan, Carbon Monoxide Production in the Small Intestine after Tin Protoporphyrin Treament.., June 1986 (Box 6)
  - Kim, Dong Hyung, An In Vivo-In Vitro Investigation of the Effect of Steroidal and Non-Steroidal Anti-Inflammatory Agents on Collagen Synthesis.., June 1986 (Box 6)
  - Kim, Gina J., Pioneer and Follower Growth Cone morphology in Developing Mammalian Cortex.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Kim, Leslie, Entrainment of Biological Rhythms: A Computer Simulation Study., Spring 1974 (Box 6)
  - Kimball, Ann, The radioisotope precipitation reaction: as a means of assay for the radiation leukimia virus.., January 17, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Kimball, Thomas Richard, The negative inotropic effects of various lanthanum ion concentrations on the chick embryo ventricle.., January 1978 (Box 6)
  - King, Donald T., Unscheduled DNA synthesis in rat skeletal muscle fibers following exposure to the monofunctional alkylating agent methyl methane sulfonate.., Spring 1971 (Box 6)
  - Kivet, William F., Culturing techniques and activity measurements of single embryonic chick ventricle cells.., March 13, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Kizer, Kenneth W., Cross-model integration phenomena in Macaca irus monkeys.., 1971-72 (Box 6)
  - Klearman, Micki, Characterization of the binding of nerve growth factor to membranes of chick embryo dorsal root ganglia and whole brain.., March 1977 (Box 6)
  - Ko, Cynthia W., The D1S1 Locus in Genetic Linkage Analysis.., 1987 (Box 6)
  - Kobashigawa, Don Kaoru, The quantitative analysis of the luteinizing hormone -- testosterone negative feedback mechanism in the adult male rat.. (Box 6)
  - Kohlstaedt, Lori, The effect of some antibiotics that inhibit protein synthesis on halobacterium halobium.., 1981 (Box 6)
  - Kolp, Lisa Ann, Effects of hippocampectomy on taste aversion conditioning in male albino rats.., March 1978 (Box 6)
  - Kosola, Kevin Ray, Adaptation by non-Native Grasses to a Local Serpentine Soil.., 1982 (Box 6)
  - Krejci, Niels C., see Suen, Patrick W.. (Box 6)
  - Kremen, Claire, Distribution of Non-Colias Pierids as a Selective Agent on a Pigment Polymorphism in Colias (Lepidoptera: Pieridae).., May 1982 (Box 6)
  - Kuo, Elo, Mu-selective Opioid Peptides with Enhanced Stability and Activity.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Lambert, Christine, Changes in Calbindin-D28k Concentration in Chronically Dissociated Granule Cells After Kindling.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Lambert, Scott Reed, The origins of Sattler's veil.., 1979 (Box 6)
  - Lanctot, Andrea, Investigating the Parameters of Myoblast TRansfer Therapy.., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Larkins, Joan Marie, Chemostimulus of ovipostion: Colias butterflies and legumes., 1978 (Box 6)
  - Larson, Carrie, Evaluation of Three Cellular RNA Extraction Methods., June 14, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Lau, Gabriel T. (Toby), Transcription Initiation of Cytochrome Oxidase Subunit III in Maize Mitochondria., 1987 (Box 6)
  - LaVeau, Paul, The isolation and preliminary characterization of a tubulin-like protein from neurospora crassa., 1976 (Box 6)
  - Layport, Cynthia Anne, Skin Conductance and Heart Rate in the Study and Treatment of Agoraphobia., 1983 (Box 6)
  - Le, An M., Automated Readings of Microlymphocytotoxic Assays., May, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Alice Jungeon, Genetic Circuits for Rhizobium Meliloti Nod Gene Regulation., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Arthur C., Mutations Conferring Moderate Streptomycin Resistance in Salmonella typhimurium Firn M7471., 1974 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Brian, Hypoxia Reduces Production of a Basement Membrane Heparan Sulfate Proteoglycan by Fetal Pulmonary Arterial Endothelial Cells., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Lee, David Charles, Effects of uridine on de novo pyrimidine biosynthesis in rat hepatoma cells in culture., April, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Lee, David M., Studies of Tumor Necrosis Factor-alpha and Class II MHC Expression in Murine Macrophages Treated with LPS and IFN-gamma., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Eric Anthony, Maturation of Membrane and Cytosolic Intestinal Aminooligopeptidase in Neonatal Rats., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Lee, Jeffrey A., NMDA Receptor Complex Labeling Using [3H]-7-N3-MK-801., June, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Lee, John Halvor, Factors Influencing Microvessel Angiogenesis., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Lee, Margaret S., Cloning the spoAIII Developmental Gene of Myxococcus Xanthus., 1987 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Rees L. III, Alpha-2 Adrenoceptor Antagonists and the Sexual Behavior of the Male Rat., 1986 (Box 6)
  - Lerner, Daniel Jeremy, The Role of Hemodynamics in Atherogenesis. I. The Effect of Elevated Shear Stress on Aortic Prostacyclin Production. II. A Cyclic Fatigue Model for Endothelial Cell Denudation., 1984 (Box 6)
  - Leung, Wesley Bing Guan, Evaluation of a new cryode design through reversible blockade of the pontine tegmentum and dorsal raphe nucleus., March, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Levine, Michael S., Regulation of glycogen metabolism in adult and larval colias eurytheme: a progress report., March, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Levinson, John R., Studies of the murine t-alleles: similarities and differences at the major histocompatibility complex., March, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Levounis, Petros, A mathematical analysis of the relative pharmacologic effect of anticholinergic and calcium blocking agents on the upper and lower urinary tract., June 9, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Levounis, Petros, A Mathematical Analysis of the Relative Pharmacological Effect of Anticholinergic and Calcium Blocking Agents on the Upper and Lower Urinary Tract., June 9, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Ley, Catherine, Balancing the Scales. Sexual Versus Natural Selection in Colias Butterflies: A Case Against Batesian Mimicry., 1988 (Box 6)
  - Lim, Greory M., Biliary Secretory IgA Levels in Rats Challenged by a Protein-Caloric., June, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Lim, Jae V., The Differential Expression of Isoforms of Myosin in Hypertrophied Myocytes in Cell Culture., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Lin, Otto Schiueh-Tzand, An Investigation of the Role of Interleuking I and Tumor Necrosis Factor in Acute Mountain Sickness., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Lin, Richard Yu-Tsang, Effects of Maternal Separation on Pubertal Development in the Squirrel Monkey., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Linsenmeyer, Todd, Coliform aerosols from sewage treatment plants., [1975] ? (Box 7)
  - Lo, Leland, The Effects of MDMA Structural ANalogs on 3H-SHT and 3H-Dopamine Release From Rat Synaptosomes., 1990 (Box 13)
  - Loehr, James P., On the termination of DNA replication in E. coli., 1975 (Box 7)
  - Loer, Curtis M., Variability in the cell death and morphology of identified neurons in grasshopper embryos., 1981 (Box 7)
  - Logerwell, Elizabeth A., Mycorrhizae and Drought Tolerance in Serpentine Plants., 1988 (Box 7)
  - Lombardi, Carolyn E., Body Composition in Congenital Heart Disease., May, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Lopez, Ricardo, Characterization of Endothelial Cells., June, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Lorenz, Robinna GAil, Decreased Concentrations of Pro-Dynorphin Derived Peptides in the Neuro-Intermediate Lobe of the Pituitary Following Dehydration., 1984 (Box 7)
  - Lowell, Clifford Arthur, Mechanism of mitochondrial DNA replication in mouse L-cells: replication of unicicular Dimer molecules., March, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Lu, Elaine, The Ratio of Collagen Type III to Type I in Rat, Monkey and Human Peripheral Nerves., 1989 (Box 13)
  - Luck, Edward E. and Green, Daniel E., A comprehensive study of two distinct forms of the Decticine Ketydid, Nebuda diabolica., May 16, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Luczak, Mary Jean, Characterizing monoclonal antibodies using meuromuscular junctions., 1981 (Box 7)
  - Lui, Fred Y. H., Territoriality and population density in the ontogenty of agonistic interactions in juvenile aequidens pulcher communities., 1975-76 (Box 7)
  - Lum, Donald Mun Bun, An investigation of the diets of two species of embiotocids (surf-fishes) in northern California. (Box 7)
  - Luskey, Barry David, Characterization of an ATPase activity found in coated vesicle preparations., 1980 (Box 7)
  - Lyles, Frank, Characterization of Membrane Protein Transfer from Radiation Leukemia Virus., 1988 (Box 7)
  - Macklin, Wendy, Isolation of a purified active cytochrome oxidase., June,1972 (Box 7)
  - Madhani, Hiten D., Alpha DNA in African Green Monkey Cells is Organized into Extremely Long Tandem Arrays., May, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Magnuson, Leif Leuthold, Biomechanics of the Tube Foot-Ampulla System in Pycnapodia helianthoides. The Tube Root of Pisaster ochraceous as a Cylindrical Pressure Vessel.., June, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Mai, Christopher H., Islet Precurson Cells., 1983 (Box 7)
  - Mai, David H., The Effect of Cyclosporin A on Islet Cells., June, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Mallett, Holly, Maternal Factors Regulating the Ontogeny of Pituitary-Adrenal Activities., June, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Malnick, Michael B., Selection for Calcium Tolerance in Neurospora Crassa Yields a Wide Variety of Circadian Clock Mutations., June 12, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Maloney, Alan, Polymorphisms in dimeric esterases of legume-feeing colias butterflies., June, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Mann, Michael O., A Computer Aided EKG Monitoring System., April, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Maoyeri, Nicole N., Effect of Torpedo Acetylcholine Receptor/Acetylcholinesterase Co-clustering Extract on the Molecular Forms of Acetylcholinesterase in Chick Muscle., September, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Margolis, Todd Paul, Foreign innervation of mammalian muscle tissue., June, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Marian, Melinda Broyles, Studies of streptomycin bleaching in Euglena Gracilis Var. Bacillaris and a resistant strain., March 15, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Mathes, Christopher W., The effects of Systematic and Intrathecal Buspirone of Sexual Behavior in Male Rats., 1988 (Box 7)
  - Matsui, Suzanne M., Effects of 7-ketocholesterol and 25-hydroxycholesterol biosynthesis in rat liver in vivo., March 1976 (Box 8)
  - McCluskey, Kevin, Circadian Rhythms in Neurospora crassa: the Effect of Valinomycin in Liquid Culture., June, 1985 (Box 8)
  - McGowan, Kelly A., A Three-Dimensional Model Simulates Events in Dermal Wound Repair., 1990 (Box 14)
  - McGraw, James Bryan, Heterogeneous leaf form in redwood: distribution and function., Winter, 1978 (Box 8)
  - McGuire, Joseph, see Suen, Patrick W.. (Box 8)
  - McIntire, Steven L., Mefford, Ivan N., Roth, Kevin A., and Barchas, Jack., The Relationship Between Cholingeric Activity and Central Serotonin Turnover., May, 1982 (Box 8)
  - McKeown, Michael, Studies on nucleoside metabolism and transport in E. coli K-12., 1975 (Box 8)
  - McMillan, Jane, Tin-Protoporphyrin Induced Suppression of Total Bilirubin Formation and Hyperilirubinemia in Adult Male Wistar Rats with Common Bile Duct Ligation., June 9, 1986 (Box 8)
  - McVittle, Jody, Properties of presynaptic inhibitory interneurons in the crayfish central nervous system., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Meade, Stephanie A., Effects of OsO4 on the Transforming Activity of PSV2-gpt DNA., 1984 (Box 8)
  - Mecham, Charles Crowford, The effects of MJ 12880-1 on phosphodiesterase activity in the liver fluke, Fasciola hepatica., 1981 (Box 8)
  - Meffert, Mollie K., Intracellular Ca Fluzes Induced by Chemotactic Peptide (FMLP) in Single Cells of a Human Monocyte/Macrophage Cell Line., June, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Menninger, Marian S., Larval Adaptation to Potential Hosts as a Determinant of Conservation Status in Two Checkerspot Butterfly Species: A Comparison of Euphydryas editha and Euphydryas chalcedona., 1984 (Box 8)
  - Merchant, Juanita Lynne, 3-Hydroxy-3-Methylglutaryl Coenzyme A Reductase in Isolated Villous and Crypt Cells of the Rat Ileum., February, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Miille, Michael J., Dissolved amino acids as a food source for metridium senile (linnaeas, 1767)., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Miille, Michael J., The uptake of amino acids from sea water by metridium senile (linnaeas, 1767)., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Milgram, Arthur J., A Study of the regulation of population size on the species Euphydryas editha by rainfall., 1987 (Box 8)
  - Milkes, David E., Arrangement of the W1 Fragment Within the W Chromosome of Schistosoma Mansoni., 1990 (Box 14)
  - Mill, Susan W., A Critical Analysis of Merous Composition in Three Populations of Lagenifera on Maui, Hawai'i., June, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Miller, Leilani M., The T Terminator of Bacteriophage Lambda., 1984 (Box 8)
  - Min, Hye Yeong, Changes in cell cycle and cell size accompanying heat survival differences in cells grown at elevated and subnormal temperatures.., 1980 (Box 8)
  - Minjarez, Debra Ann, Histamine-Induced Gap Formation in Monolayer Cultures of Human Skin Microvascular Endothelial Cells.., 1988 (Box 8)
  - Mintz, Leslie Joy, Measurement of sequential changes in left ventricular function following coronary artery bypass graft surgery.., January 1979 (Box 8)
  - Miyajima, Debra L., Biochemical and genetic studies of the Mg++Ca++ATPase of Escherichia coli.., June 1976 (Box 8)
  - Miyamoto, Michael I., Cardiovascular Effects of Injections of L-glutamate into the Paraventricualar Nucleus of the Rat.., 1988 (Box 8)